Hello everyone my self
here neither any educational qualification
criteria nor
any experience is required here along
with that you don't need any laptop here
and means even if you are 10th pass you
can apply here completely work from
home so we will know all your details in this video
before that if you like this video then
definitely like the video and
definitely subscribe to the channel so that you can get
all the notifications along with the
bank their join which is
showing general insurance and the job
profile here and become a general insurance
agent is a very simple application process
here you enter your mobile number enter your
email id and enter your full name
and you download the app here now
here
exactly means you will know about what will be your benefits
first of all this is a zero investment
business you don't have to invest even a single penny here
if you work well then
you can earn a commission of up to 85000 here monthly
and issues policy instantly
online means  Here at your SN
Insurance Agent, you do not have to do any paperwork, it will be done
directly online, the
work here is completely flexible, you can work
here as per your convenience, it is
not necessary that you have to give 4 hours a day or
8 hours a day here and here
you have to work directly with ICC Long Part, no
agent has to work
with it and here
as I mentioned there is no
paperwork here because the policies are instantly
online here and you will get commission here on your time
and along with that
they have given a chart here for understanding
where you can understand that if you take car
insurance
then you will get your commission 15%, if the date is
around 3000 then
you will get 15% of it,
if their premium is 15000 then you will get 15%,
is a very good company for example
in car and bike insurance,
so I think any student and housewife
or retired professional who
wants to do some business from home,  This is also a very
good opportunity because the
commission here is also very good, there is 15% commission here
and from a very general company because the
insurance was vehicle insurance,
ICICI Lombard has a very good name
because it is very genuine for vehicle
insurance, so definitely apply to apply
but I am giving it in the description box, so
friends, see you
in my next video, latest